Turn your idea into a real business with Plasso. Selling your physical or digital products
couldn't be easier. There's no need to setup a 'store', every product you create get it's own
dedicated payment page, called a Space, that you can link to from your website, Facebook
page, Twitter profile, etc. Or use F'laSSi:i Emt:iei:l: to put the payment form directly in your
own existing web pages, you'Iljust need to paste a small snippet of code into your HTML.
Plasso is built to handle all types of payments: One-Time payments, Recurring payments,
Pre-Orders, Invoices, Donations and more.
Plasso uses=:tf‘lpe, the world's best and most secure payment platform, to handle all
transactions. Don't have a Stripe account? No problem. You'II be able to set one up with our
1-step sign up process.
